Guide to the New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records, [ca.1875]-1981.
New York State College of Agriculture and Life Sciences. Office of Academic Programs records
- Alfred M. S. Pridham Scholarships, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 50)
- Corwith Memorial Endowment Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 10, Folder 51)
- Agricultural Alumni Endowment Fund, 1967-1973 (Box 10, Folder 52)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Development Fund, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 53)
- Agriculture and Life Sciences Development Fund, 1972-1976 (Box 10, Folder 54)
- Frederick F. Horton Scholarship, 1968 (Box 10, Folder 55)
- Loblaw Scholarships, 1968-1969 (Box 10, Folder 56)
- H. B. Munger Memorial Endowment, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Turnstyle Retailing Scholarship, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- GolF Course Superintendents Association of America, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- New York Rural Rehabiitation Corporation Scholarship, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 4)
- Eastern Dairy-Deli Association Scholarship, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Ellis L. Phillips Foundation, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Bill Hotaling Scholarship Endowment Fund, 1967-1969 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Fannie B. Miller Scholarship, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Bertha Manent Endowment Fund, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Students Loan Fund, 1914-1926 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Agricultural Students Loan Fund, 1927-1943 (Box 11, Folder 11)
- Max Schling Loan Fund, 1925-1966 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- American Agriculturis Foundation, 1937-1941 (Box 11, Folder 13)
- Miscellaneous, 1922-1963 (Box 11, Folder 14)
- Winter Course Loan Fund, 1939-1950 (Box 11, Folder 15)
- Teacher's Placement Service, 1920-1930 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Financial Aid for Students, 1953-1962 (Box 11, Folder 17)
- Livestock Advisory Council, 1962 (Box 11, Folder 18)
- Miscellaneous Orders or Rulings on Procedure, 1920-1970 (Box 11, Folder 19)
- Ombudsman, 1969-1974 (Box 11, Folder 20)
- Human Affairs Program, 1970-1975 (Box 11, Folder 21)
- Cornell United Religious Work, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 22)
- Center for International Studies, 1971-1972 (Box 11, Folder 23)
- Summer Workshop - Education Management, 1970 (Box 11, Folder 24)
- Study Opportunities - Gradute Schools, 1971 (Box 11, Folder 25)
- Venture Program, 1975 (Box 11, Folder 26)
- Work Study Program, 1944-1974 (Box 11, Folder 27)
- Environmental Science Center at Cornell, 1968-1971 (Box 11, Folder 28)
- Statement on Environmental Education, 1970-1973 (Box 11, Folder 29)
- Home Study Program, 1971-1975 (Box 11, Folder 30)
- Career Development Program, 1971-1976 (Box 11, Folder 31)
- Sea Grant Program, 1970-1974 (Box 11, Folder 32)
- Environmental Studies Program, 1966-1976 (Box 11, Folder 33)
- Council for Agricultural Science and Technology, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 34)
- Veterans Affairs, 1972-1974 (Box 11, Folder 35)
- Cornell Institute for Research in Occupational and Career Education, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 36)
- Communication Specialists for Population Affairs Project, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 37)
- Northeast Regional Center for Rural Development, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 38)
- SUNY - Empire State College Programs, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 39)
- Energy Crisis, 1973 (Box 11, Folder 40)
- Natural Resources Committee, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 41)
- Food science Review, 1973-1976 (Box 11, Folder 42)
- Boyce Thompson Institute for Plant Research, 1973-1975 (Box 11, Folder 43)
- Aquaculture Program at Cornell, 1974 (Box 11, Folder 44)
- Admission of Students - General Requirements, 1919-1970 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Foreign Students, 1934-1941 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Rating of Other Institutions, 1921-1934 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- SUNY Transfer Students, 1967-1969 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- SUNY Articulation Conference - Mohawk Valley Community College, 1969-1973 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Transfers within the University, 1940-1972 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Education Practices Act, 1948-1966 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Advanced Standing Credit - Transfer Students, 1944-1973 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- College Admissions Assistance Center, 1964 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Committee on Admissions, 1972 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Selection of Students, 1927-1967 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Recruitment, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Graduation Requirements, 1895-1973 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- College Curriculum Committee, 1973-1974 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Curriculum - General, 1919-1955 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Extension Workers, 1930-1959 (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Greenskeeper and Turf Experts, 1921-1922 (Box 12, Folder 17)
- School for Canners Field Men, 1947-1950 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Science Teachers, 1943-1956 (Box 12, Folder 19)
- New York State Science Congress, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Curriculum for Rural Ministers, 1944-1952 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Extramural Courses, 1945-1967 (Box 12, Folder 22)
- International Training Administration - Chinese Trainees, 1945-1946 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- New York Institute for Public Welfare Training, 1946-1947 (Box 12, Folder 24)
- Bankers School of Agriculture, 1946-1959 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Technical Education in Agriculture and Natural Resources, 1945-1968 (Box 12, Folder 26)
- Food Processing, 1944-1960 (Box 12, Folder 27)
- Pre-Veterinary Curriculum, 1948-1961 (Box 12, Folder 28)
- Five-Year Agricultural Engineering Program, 1951-1962 (Box 12, Folder 29)
- Biological Science Curriculum, 1958-1964 (Box 12, Folder 30)
- Food Distribution, 1957-1959 (Box 12, Folder 31)
- Vocational Agriculture, 1952-1975 (Box 12, Folder 32)
- Agricultural Business, 1961-1964 (Box 12, Folder 33)
- Pre-Medical Curriculum, 1960-1974 (Box 12, Folder 34)
- Vocational Education, 1962-1963 (Box 12, Folder 35)
- Vocational Education, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Vocational Education Meeting - Lincoln Nebraska, 1968 (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Curriculum in Outdoor Recreation Resources, 1964-1966 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Cornell Marine Biology, 1968-1976 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Cornell Marine Biology, 1968-1976 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Undergraduate Program in International Agriculture, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Agricultural Sciences, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Science, Technology and Society, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Teacher Training Program, 1956 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Field Practice in Entomology, 1934-1940 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Residence Requirements, 1914-1969 (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Mental Ability Tests, 1920-1959 (Box 13, Folder 12)
- University Testing Service, 1939-1960 (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Personnel Work, 1925-1944 (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Freshman Week, 1929-1964 (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Vocational Guidance, 1930-1959 (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Cornell Day, 1942-1969 (Box 13, Folder 17)
- Orientation, 1922-1929 (Box 13, Folder 18)
- Placement - General, 1937-1971 (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Positions in Correctional Institutions, 1938 (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Mathematics, 1946-1962 (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Excuses, 1960-1969 (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Absences, Class Trips, 1917-1955 (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Class Size, 1929-1930 (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Grading in the College of Agriculture, 1966-1970 (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Distribution of Grades, 1934-1970 (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Mid-Term Grades, 1964 (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Grades and Grading, 1915-1976 (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Non-Degree Courses, 1943-1952 (Box 13, Folder 29)
- Special Students, 1909-1965 (Box 13, Folder 30)
- Combined Course in Agriculture and Veterinary Medicine, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 31)
- Agriculture - Business and Public Administration, 1941-1957 (Box 13, Folder 32)
- School of Nutrition, 1942-1973 (Box 13, Folder 33)
- Division of Nutritional Studies, 1974-1976 (Box 13, Folder 34)
- Examinations, 1903-1969 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Examinations - Entrance, 1929 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Examinations - College Credit, 1935-1939 (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Examinations Schedule, 1960-1965 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Examinations - Aptitude and Achievement, 1968-1976 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- Examinations - Conduct, 1947-1952 (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Publications and Printing, 1917-1974 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- College Announcemnts, 1950-1972 (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Publicity, 1928-1968 (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Prize Competitions, 1941-1964 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Ring Memorial, 1928-1967 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Charles Lathrop Pack Foundation - Forestry, 1922-1944 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Alumni, 1918-1971 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Merrill-Palmer, 1925-1940 (Box 14, Folder 14)
- Sharples Scholarship, 191-1922 (Box 14, Folder 15)
- New York Times, 1926 (Box 14, Folder 16)
- James Manufacturing Company, 1920 (Box 14, Folder 17)
- Frank Morrison Awards, 1959-1969 (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Alpha Zeta Scholarship, 1931-1959 (Box 14, Folder 19)
- Eastman Contest Winners, 1923-1976 (Box 14, Folder 20)
- Samuel Stewart Essay Contest, 1922-1969 (Box 14, Folder 21)
- Vegetable Growers Contest, 1930 (Box 14, Folder 22)
- Judging Contests, 1952-1966 (Box 14, Folder 23)
- Swift College Essay Contest, 1952 (Box 14, Folder 24)
- Dimock Memorial Fund, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 25)
- Credit Hours of Instruction, 1914-1957 (Box 14, Folder 26)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1914-1920 (Box 14, Folder 27)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1921-1925 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1925-1929 (Box 14, Folder 29)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1929-1932 (Box 14, Folder 30)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1932-1935 (Box 14, Folder 31)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1935-1938 (Box 14, Folder 32)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1938-1941 (Box 14, Folder 33)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1941-1944 (Box 14, Folder 34)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1944-1947 (Box 14, Folder 35)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1948-1951 (Box 14, Folder 36)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1951-1954 (Box 14, Folder 37)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1954-1957 (Box 15, Folder 1)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1957-1960 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1960-1963 (Box 15, Folder 3)
- Student Hours of Instruction, 1963-1967 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- Class Lists by Registration, 1912-1944 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Daily Class Schedule, 1928-1971 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Distribution of Hours of Instruction, 1954-1957 (Box 15, Folder 7)
- Student Scholarships and Awards, 1913-1973 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Miscellaneous Data on Students, 1928-1955 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Cost of Services, 1929-1962 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Two Year Courses, 1933-1968 (Box 15, Folder 11)
- Cost of Instruction to Students, 1929-1960 (Box 15, Folder 12)
- One Year Course, 1966-1971 (Box 15, Folder 13)
- Book Lists, 1934-1936 (Box 15, Folder 14)
- Student Photographs, 1938 (Box 15, Folder 15)
- Applications for Positions, 1960-1964 (Box 15, Folder 16)
- Registration, 1933-1971 (Box 15, Folder 17)
- Relation to Secondary Schools, 1929 (Box 15, Folder 18)
- Students Entering the College of Agriculture, 1911-1957 (Box 15, Folder 19)
- Numbering of Courses, 1941-1963 (Box 15, Folder 20)
- Credit for Extension Courses, 1921-1934 (Box 15, Folder 21)
- Television, 1955-1968 (Box 15, Folder 22)
- Requirements for Teachers Certificates, 1920-1965 (Box 15, Folder 23)
- Recommendations of Farmers in Indian Service, 1916 (Box 15, Folder 24)
- Capper Awards, 1930 (Box 15, Folder 25)
- Faculty - General, 1947-1953 (Box 15, Folder 26)
- Faculty Legislation, 1920-1966 (Box 15, Folder 27)
- Faculty Advisers, 1927-1964 (Box 15, Folder 28)
- Advisory Committee on Advisory System, 1960-1971 (Box 15, Folder 29)
- Handbook for Advisors, 1959-1965 (Box 15, Folder 30)
- Faculty Committees, 1946-1958 (Box 15, Folder 31)
- Publications Committee, 1969-1971 (Box 15, Folder 32)
- Publications Committee, 1960-1968 (Box 15, Folder 33)
- Publications Committee, 1971-1974 (Box 15, Folder 34)
- Publications Committee, 1974-1977 (Box 15, Folder 35)
- University Faculty Committee on Student Affairs, 1963 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- Scholarships, 1956 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Advisory Committee on Admissions, 1959-1961 (Box 16, Folder 3)
- Committee on Requirements for Graduation, 1944-1965 (Box 16, Folder 4)
- Committee on Petitions, 1961-1965 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- University Faculty Commmittee on Military Curricula, 1961-1971 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1919-1960 (Box 16, Folder 7)
- Committee on Educational Policy Review, 1958 (Box 16, Folder 8)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1956-1959 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Committee on Educational Policy, 1960-1961 (Box 16, Folder 10)
- Committee on Entrance Credentials, 1962 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Committee on Conferences, 1963-1970 (Box 16, Folder 12)
- Film Committee, 1961-1975 (Box 16, Folder 13)
- Nominations Committee, 1967-1975 (Box 16, Folder 14)
- Nominations Committee, 1974-1975 (Box 16, Folder 15)
- Nominations Committee, 1973-1977 (Box 16, Folder 16)
- Student Elections, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 17)
- Student Elections, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 18)
- Student Elections, 1975-1977 (Box 16, Folder 19)
- English Proficiency, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
- Committee on International Exchange of Persons, 1968-1972 (Box 16, Folder 21)
- University Policy Committee, 1917-1958 (Box 16, Folder 22)
- Statistics, 1896-1921 (Box 16, Folder 23)
- Statistics, 1922-1925 (Box 16, Folder 24)
- Statistics, 1925-1926 (Box 16, Folder 25)
- Statistics, 1926-1927 (Box 16, Folder 26)
- Statistics, 1927-1928 (Box 16, Folder 27)
- Statistics, 1928-1929 (Box 16, Folder 28)
- Statistics, 1929-1930 (Box 16, Folder 29)
- Statistics, 1930-1931 (Box 16, Folder 30)
- Statistics, 1931-1932 (Box 16, Folder 31)
- Statistics, 1932-1933 (Box 16, Folder 32)
- Statistics, 1933-1934 (Box 16, Folder 33)
- Statistics, 1934-1935 (Box 16, Folder 34)
- Statistics, 1935-1936 (Box 16, Folder 35)
- Statistics, 1936-1937 (Box 17, Folder 1)
- Statistics, 1937-1938 (Box 17, Folder 2)
- Statistics, 1938-1939 (Box 17, Folder 3)
- Statistics, 1939-1940 (Box 17, Folder 4)
- Statistics, 1940-1941 (Box 17, Folder 5)
- Statistics, 1941-1942 (Box 17, Folder 6)
- Statistics, 1942-1943 (Box 17, Folder 7)
- Statistics, 1943-1944 (Box 17, Folder 8)
- Statistics, 1944-1945 (Box 17, Folder 9)
- Statistics, 1945-1947 (Box 17, Folder 10)
- Miscellaneous Faculty Statistics, 1964 (Box 17, Folder 11)
- Present and Past Faculty Members, 1965 (Box 17, Folder 12)
- Institutional Studies, 1969 (Box 17, Folder 13)
- Grievance Procedure, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 14)
- Sebbatic Leave, 1912-1971 (Box 17, Folder 15)
- Salaries and Ranks, 1912-1973 (Box 17, Folder 16)
- Duties and Powers, 1915-1951 (Box 17, Folder 17)
- Professional Improvement, 1970 (Box 17, Folder 18)
- Time Distribution, 1925-1965 (Box 17, Folder 19)
- Teaching Load, 1915-1948 (Box 17, Folder 20)
- Promotional Material, 17-21 (Box 17, Folder 21)
- Appointments and Promotions, 1937-1968 (Box 17, Folder 22)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1940-1972 (Box 17, Folder 23)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1972-1973 (Box 17, Folder 24)
- Traveling Fellowships, 1973-1976 (Box 17, Folder 25)
- Employment Policy, 1960-1969 (Box 17, Folder 26)
- Office of Resident Instruction, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 27)
- Professor Merit Award, 1947-1963 (Box 17, Folder 28)
- Private Consulting, 1953-1965 (Box 17, Folder 29)
- American-German Cooperation in Agricultural Research, 1957 (Box 17, Folder 30)
- Inter-College Compensation Policy, 1965-1970 (Box 17, Folder 31)
- Professors-At-Large Program, 1970-1974 (Box 17, Folder 32)
- Intercultural Studies Information, 1972 (Box 17, Folder 33)
- Agricultural Economics, 1932-1972 (Box 17, Folder 34)
- Agricultural Economics, 1968-1976 (Box 17, Folder 35)
- Agricultural Economics Course Review, 1973-1976 (Box 18, Folder 1)
- Agricultural Engineering, 1944-1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Engineering Courses, 1967-1968 (Box 18, Folder 3)
- Agronomy, 1942-1969 (Box 18, Folder 4)
- Agronomy, 1067-1976 (Box 18, Folder 5)
- Agronomy Research Reports, 1973-1975 (Box 18, Folder 6)
- Animal Husbandry, 1935 (Box 18, Folder 7)
- Department of Animal Sciences, 1968-1976 (Box 18, Folder 8)
- Bailey Hortorium, 1935-1973 (Box 18, Folder 9)
- Biochemistry, 1938-1963 (Box 18, Folder 10)
- Summer School of Biology, 1924-1934 (Box 38, Folder 11)
- Botany, 1933-1964 (Box 18, Folder 12)
- Conservation Programs, 1948-1963 (Box 18, Folder 13)
- Department of Conservation, 1967-1975 (Box 18, Folder 14)
- Department of Conservation, 1970-1971 (Box 18, Folder 15)
- Conservation Comments, 1971-1974 (Box 18, Folder 16)
- Conservation Correspondence, 1944-1948 (Box 18, Folder 17)
- Natural Resources, 1974-1975 (Box 18, Folder 18)
- Natural Resources, 1974-1977 (Box 18, Folder 19)
- Committee on Dairy Industry, 1944-1951 (Box 19, Folder 1)
- Dairy Industry, 1951-1972 (Box 19, Folder 2)
- Food Science, 1932-1975 (Box 19, Folder 3)
- Entomology, 1929-1964 (Box 19, Folder 4)
- Entomology, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 5)
- Entomology, 1970-1973 (Box 19, Folder 6)
- Search Committee for Department of Entomology Chairman, 1972 (Box 19, Folder 7)
- Extension Service - Appointments, 1940-1955 (Box 19, Folder 8)
- Communication Arts, 1945-1975 (Box 19, Folder 9)
- Communication Arts -Graduate Program, 1965-1969 (Box 19, Folder 10)
- Communication Arts - Ward, 1965-1975 (Box 19, Folder 11)
- Floriculture and Ornamental Horticulture, 1931-1976 (Box 19, Folder 12)
- Landscape Architecture, 1971-1972 (Box 19, Folder 13)
- Landscape Architecture Curriculum, 1968-1975 (Box 19, Folder 14)
- Landscape Architecture, 1967-1968 (Box 19, Folder 15)
- Landscape Architecture, 1970-1976 (Box 20, Folder 1)
- Landscape Architecture, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 2)
- Landscape Artchitecture, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 3)
- Landscape Artchitecture, 1976 (Box 20, Folder 4)
- Floriculture, 1970-1975 (Box 20, Folder 5)
- Forestry, 1929-1937 (Box 20, Folder 6)
- Forestry Students, 1922-1936 (Box 20, Folder 7)
- Geneva Agricultural Experiment Station, 1941-1955 (Box 20, Folder 8)
- Home Economics, 1938-1971 (Box 20, Folder 9)
- Library, 1933-1974 (Box 20, Folder 10)
- Meterology, 1949-1971 (Box 20, Folder 11)
- Plant Breeding, 1941-1976 (Box 20, Folder 12)
- Biometry, 1968-1975 (Box 20, Folder 13)
- Biometrics, 1949-1962 (Box 20, Folder 14)
- Department of Plant Breeding, 1966-1975 (Box 20, Folder 15)
- Plant Pathology, 1942-1963 (Box 20, Folder 16)
- Plant Pathology, 1968-1976 (Box 20, Folder 17)
- Pomology, 1969-1976 (Box 20, Folder 18)
- Poultry Science, 1940-1975 (Box 20, Folder 19)
- Animal Science - Genetics Courses, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 20)
- Survey: Plant - Animal Heredity Courses, 1973-1974 (Box 20, Folder 21)
- Vegetable Crops, 1940-1964 (Box 20, Folder 22)
- Vegetable crops, 1967-1976 (Box 20, Folder 23)
- Education, 1932-1959 (Box 21, Folder 1)
- Education, 1960-1976 (Box 21, Folder 2)
- Department of Education - Special Problems, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 3)
- Special Committee - Department of Education, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 4)
- Two-Year College Development Program, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 5)
- Rural Sociology, 1932-1976 (Box 21, Folder 6)
- Rural Sociology, 1967-1973 (Box 21, Folder 7)
- Social Sciences - General Review, 1969-1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
- Wildlife Conservation, 1935-1944 (Box 21, Folder 9)
- Zoology, 1941-1948 (Box 21, Folder 10)
- Improvement in Instruction, 1922-1969 (Box 21, Folder 11)
- Resident Instruction, 1922-1969 (Box 21, Folder 12)
- Evaluation of Instruction, 1967-1968 (Box 21, Folder 13)
- Measurement of Effects, 1928 (Box 21, Folder 14)
- Freshman Orientation, 1922-1958 (Box 21, Folder 15)
- Orientation, 1960-1968 (Box 21, Folder 16)
- Orientation, 1968 (Box 21, Folder 17)
- Orientation, 1968-1970 (Box 21, Folder 18)
- Orientation, 1970 (Box 21, Folder 19)
- Orientation, 1971 (Box 21, Folder 20)
- Media Services, 1975 (Box 21, Folder 21)
- Classrooms, 1962-1965 (Box 21, Folder 22)
- Degrees and Certificates, 1932-1970 (Box 22, Folder 1)
- Lists - Two Year Certificates, 1933-1958 (Box 22, Folder 2)
- Lists - Winter Course Certificates, 1929-1938 (Box 22, Folder 3)
- Lists - Agriculture Graduation Ballots, 1941-1966 (Box 22, Folder 4)
- Copies of Diplomas and Certificates, 1962-1964 (Box 22, Folder 5)
- Summary of Degrees, 1913-1972 (Box 22, Folder 6)
- Enrollment - University, 1914-1965 (Box 22, Folder 7)
- Enrollment - Agriculture and Home Economics, 1905-1929 (Box 22, Folder 8)
- Enrollment - Agriculture, 1922-1966 (Box 22, Folder 9)
- Agriculture: Non-residents, 1922-1976 (Box 22, Folder 10)
- Enrollment Projections, 1967 (Box 22, Folder 11)
- Agriculture - Foreign Students, 1923-1971 (Box 22, Folder 12)
- Agriculture - Women, 1915-1972 (Box 22, Folder 13)
- Graduate Students, 1921-1966 (Box 22, Folder 14)
- Agriculture - Counties of New York, 1947-1952 (Box 22, Folder 15)
- Agriculture - Morality, withdrawsls, 1914-1948 (Box 22, Folder 16)
- Hotel Administration - General, 1922-1932 (Box 22, Folder 17)
- Summer School - General, 1929-1969 (Box 22, Folder 18)
- Summer Session, 1926 (Box 22, Folder 19)
- Summer Session, 1927 (Box 22, Folder 20)
- Summer Session, 1928 (Box 22, Folder 21)
- Summer Session, 1929 (Box 22, Folder 22)
- Summer Session, 1930 (Box 22, Folder 23)
- Summer Session, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 24)
- Summer Session, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 25)
- Summer Session, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 26)
- Summer Session, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 27)
- Summer Session, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 28)
- Summer Session, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 29)
- Summer Session, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 30)
- Summer Session, 1966-1968 (Box 22, Folder 31)
- Summer Session, 1927-1962 (Box 22, Folder 32)
- Summer Session - Agriculture, 1912-1975 (Box 22, Folder 33)
- Short Schools, 1918-1957 (Box 22, Folder 34)
- Winter Courses, 1892-1962 (Box 22, Folder 35)
- Enrollments of other Institutions, 1920-1956 (Box 22, Folder 36)
- Enrollment - Future, 1954-1963 (Box 22, Folder 37)
- Tuition, 1931 (Box 22, Folder 38)
- Tuition, 1932 (Box 22, Folder 39)
- Tuition, 1933 (Box 22, Folder 40)
- Tuition, 1934 (Box 22, Folder 41)
- Tuition, 1935 (Box 22, Folder 42)
- Tuition, 1936 (Box 22, Folder 43)
- Tuition, 1937 (Box 22, Folder 44)
- Tuition, 1938 (Box 22, Folder 45)
- Tuition, 1939 (Box 22, Folder 46)
- Tuition, 1940 (Box 22, Folder 47)
- Tuition, 1941 (Box 22, Folder 48)
- Students Held for Tuition, 1929-1931 (Box 22, Folder 49)
- Tuition and Fees - General, 1913-1956 (Box 22, Folder 50)
- Tuition and Fees - General, 1956-1974 (Box 22, Folder 51)
- Laboratory Fees, 1928-1930 (Box 23, Folder 1)
- Laboratory Fees, 1930-1931 (Box 23, Folder 2)
- Laboratory Fees, 1931-1932 (Box 23, Folder 3)
- Laboratory Fees, 1932-1933 (Box 23, Folder 4)
- Laboratory Fees, 1933-1934 (Box 23, Folder 5)
- Laboratory Fees, 1934-1935 (Box 23, Folder 6)
- Laboratory Fees, 1935-1936 (Box 23, Folder 7)
- Laboratory Fees, 1936-1937 (Box 23, Folder 8)
- Laboratory Fees, 1937-1938 (Box 23, Folder 9)
- Laboratory Fees, 1938-1939 (Box 23, Folder 10)
- Laboratory Fees, 1918-1953 (Box 23, Folder 11)
- Laboratory Fees, 1953-1963 (Box 23, Folder 12)
- Laboratory Fees, 1964-1974 (Box 23, Folder 13)
- Makeup Fees, 1956-1973 (Box 23, Folder 14)
- Tuition for SUNY Faculty for Courses at Cornell, 1969 (Box 23, Folder 15)
- Tuition for Graduate Student Assistants, 1913-1970 (Box 23, Folder 16)
- Tuition and Residence, 1912-1971 (Box 23, Folder 17)
- Tuition and Fees in other Institutions, 1960 (Box 23, Folder 18)
- Tuition for Excess Hours, 1926-1938 (Box 23, Folder 19)
- Tuition on Transfer, 1930-1960 (Box 23, Folder 20)
- Tuition for Children of Staff Members, 1939-1958 (Box 23, Folder 21)
- Administration Fee, 1937 (Box 23, Folder 22)
- Composite Fee, 1951-1964 (Box 23, Folder 23)
- Reinstatement Fee, 1927 (Box 23, Folder 24)
- Late Registration Fee, 1936-1973 (Box 23, Folder 25)
- Summer School Staff and Salaries, 1931-1935 (Box 23, Folder 26)
- Third Term Proposals, 1921-1956 (Box 23, Folder 27)
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1913-1915 (Box 23, Folder 28)
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1920 (Box 23, Folder 29)
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1921 (Box 23, Folder 30)
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1922 (Box 23, Folder 31)
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1923 (Box 23, Folder 32)
- Lists of Summer Session Students, 1924 (Box 23, Folder 33)